紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   草草
時間軸   紙袋PPPPP
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第三集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
總統終于通過了法案
為什么不認命阿布佐
謝潑德堂
是你在刺激他們
You are daring them.
是你把事情鬧大了  現在他們不肯罷休了
You've turned it into a spectacle, and now they will not stop.
相信我  這些人不會罷休的
Believe me. These people will not rest.
你得做出彌補
You need to make amends.
為對她的輕慢嗎
For slighting her?
-為指出他們嗎  -你得給他們點什么
- For identifying them? - You have to give them something.
-我不相信這份法案  -該死的
- I don't believe in the bill. - Oh, goddamn it!
這份法案  你在聽嗎
This bill. Are you listening?
-我是文森特·阿布佐  -第九巡回法院
- Vincent Abruzzo. - Ninth Circuit.
我很高興總統辦公室總算迎來一位女性
I'm so glad that we finally have a woman in the Oval Office.
我們的命運一直糾纏在一起
And we've been entwined, you and I,
不管愿不愿意
like it or not,
這幾十年來都是如此
for decades now.
我們有權分道揚鑣了
We deserve to go our separate ways.
問題是  我們有個緊急的問題要處理
The problem is we have something urgent to attend to
凱茜·杜蘭特
called Cathy Durant.
然后我們就終于自由了
And then we can finally be free.
你需要我的幫助
Now, you need my help.
今晚晚些時候
Later tonight,
我要眼看著你簽署
I'm going to watch you sign that bill
你桌上的那份法案
that's sitting on your desk.
"對于死者  王國毫無意義"
"To the dead, a kingdom means nothing."
我沒進行過獸交
I never had sex with a farm animal
也沒虐待過女友  除非娶了她算虐待
or abused a girlfriend, unless you count marrying her.
但是  這的確不易
Let me say, it was tough, uh...
選出十件我最重要的案子
narrowing down my ten most significant cases.
我更喜歡那些小問題
I prefer the smaller questions.
關于我加入的專業組織  我的教學
Of my professional memberships, my teaching.
總統女士  就跟你說一句
Madam President, just between you and me,
我認為這事沒有有些人說的那么遙不可及
my feeling is that it's not as far-fetched as some people say.
我依然認為
I still think there is a universe
《平權修正案》是可以通過的
where the ERA gets passed.
女人真是最了不起了  是吧
Women truly are the best, aren't they?
我很榮幸能成為繼任大法官候選人
I am deeply honored to be considered for the late Justice's seat.
告訴我
So, tell me.
他們怎么買通你的  謝潑德家族
How did they buy you? The Shepherds.
阿布佐法官  總統女士  抱歉打擾了
Judge Abruzzo, Madam President, I hate to break this up.
我已經占用了
I have already taken
總統太多的寶貴時間了
too much of the president's valuable time.
總統女士
Madam President.
-副總統先生  -法官大人
- Mr. Vice President. - Your Honor.
我真的非常榮幸
It has been a sincere pleasure.
我把邁克爾斯法官安排在明天下班前
I'll set up Judge Michaels for the end of the day tomorrow?
杜蘭特國務卿在等你
I have Secretary Durant waiting for you.
我覺得很無力
I felt emasculated.
什么
Excuse me.
比爾·謝潑德把著我的手
Bill Shepherd guiding my hand.
你看上去也很無力  馬克
And you looked emasculated, Mark.
-你錯了  -不  我沒錯
- You're mistaken. - No, I'm not mistaken.
我看到你的表情了
I watched your face.
-總統女士  -別那么喊我了
- Madam President-- -Please don't call me that. Please.
-克萊爾  -這個好點
- Claire. - Better.
-克萊爾  -怎么了
- Claire. - Yes. What?
那場斗爭你贏不了的
That was not a fight you were gonna win.
-你喜歡當信使嗎  -什么
- Do you like being the messenger? - What?
這是你從小的夢想嗎
Has it been a dream of some sort since you were a little boy?
因為我可以告訴你
Because I can tell you something.
一旦你認清你是多么受局限
Once you identify the degree to which you are boxed in,
就會覺得無比釋然
you'll see how liberating it is.
你是我這邊的
Are you with me...
還是你結交的那些無恥之徒
or are you with those horrible, horrible people
那邊的
you've attached yourself to?
因為我可以告訴你關于比爾·謝潑德的一點
Because I can tell you something about Bill Shepherd.
我能從他身上聞出來
I could smell it on him.
我曾在我父親  母親身上聞到過那味兒
The way I could on my father, on my mother.
他病了
He's sick.
-他已經好了  -還病著呢
- Well, he was. - He is.
然后你怎么辦
And then where will that leave you?
只剩她了
With her?
安奈特·謝潑德
Annette Shepherd?
我清楚那女人的本事
I know what that woman is,
更重要的是  沒什么本事
and more to the point, isn't capable of.
還有跟阿布佐法官在籌款晚宴上
And that little encounter with the honorable Judge Abruzzo
偶然相遇  也是安排好的吧
at the fundraiser, that was orchestrated too, wasn't it?
是的
Yes.
我有時看著他  會想象他六歲時的樣子
I look at him sometimes and imagine him at six years old.
他一直這么慎重
Was he always so deliberative?
小心嗎
Cautious?
我覺得換了別的人生
And I think in another life...
在別的情況下
some other context
我們或許還能成為朋友
might we have been friends.
你該決定了  馬克
It's time to decide, Mark.
我衡量每位總統的標準都一樣
I hold every president to the same standard.
你是讓美國變好了
Are you making America better,
還是變差了
or are you making America worse?
這才是唯一重要的
That's all that matters...
抱歉  你可以把這個關掉嗎
Excuse me. Could you turn this off, please?
-好的  先生  -這個城市的言論水平啊
- Yes, sir. - The level of discourse in this city.
告訴你  她說得對
I'm telling you. She does have a point.
你得叫鄧肯
You need to tell Duncan
對他的斗牛犬留點神
to be careful when it comes to his pit bull.
城市
City.
小羅斯福把這地方變成了一座城市
FDR turned this place into a city.
他的各種機構  辦事員
With his agencies and armies of clerks.
還有隨即而至的教授
All the professors that followed.
戰前  這里就是個南方小鎮
Before the war, this was just a small Southern town.
雖然是大理石建的  但是
One built of marble, yeah, but just a...
也只是個沼澤邊的小鎮
small town sitting on a swamp.
可以來玩
Place to visit.
可以來
Place to...
保護共和制
protect the Republic.
保護各州權利
Secure States' rights.
可不像今天這樣
That's not what it is today.
徹底淪為官僚  說客
Some top-down money grab for bureaucrats,
和整個民主黨搶錢的地方
lobbyists and the entire Democratic party.
分別是第26任[共和黨]和32任[民主黨]總統
兩人是遠親
你一直更喜歡老羅斯福
You've always been more Teddy.
比那個叛徒小羅斯福強
Than that traitor pig Franklin?
我知道對于你來說  來華盛頓是種犧牲
Look, I know it's a sacrifice for you to be here, in Washington.
但老天爺啊  為什么要住他當初住的房間
But for God's sake, why take the same room he was in?
這個嘛
Well--
他是想盯著她
Well, he wanted to keep an eye on her.
弗蘭西斯放不下白宮
Francis never could let go of the White House.
但他給了我們一個我們一直在等待的機會
But he did give us the opportunity we've been waiting for.
她不夠格
She's not qualified.
總統之位是她偷來的
She stole the damn thing.
如果說有一個
If ever there was ever a chance
縮小政府規模的機會
to shrink the office down to size,
那就是趁克萊爾·安德伍德在職的時候
it's the presidency of Claire Underwood.
或許你是該去競選
Maybe you should run for office.
那個時機已經過去了
I think that time has passed.
我擔心你
I'm worried about you.
不用
Oh, don't be.
我好極了
Never better.
去監管法案只是個開頭  還有數百份
Deregulation bill is the first of a hundred,
都蓄勢待發
ready and waiting.
你的行動速度
The speed you're moving at--
我可以待會兒再來  律師就要來了
I can come back. The lawyers are due any minute.
沒事  進來吧  自己倒點什么喝
No, no. Come on in here. Grab yourself a cup of something.
我知道安奈特想在其他人到來前
I know Annette wanted to talk to you in person,
當面跟你談談
before the rest of the team arrives.
我把你告訴我的關于總統的事轉告她了
I passed on what you told me about the president.
我希望鄧肯拿到前
I want you to have it all before
讓你先知道
Duncan got his hands on it.
她承認了三次墮胎
She admitted to all three of the abortions.
但我可以查到孩子都分別是誰的
But I can get you the names of the men. Who they were.
不  我不喜歡這樣
No, I'm not comfortable with this.
我們暫且不談這個了
Let's take that off the table for now.
她會配合的
She'll play along.
我們會確保的
We'll make sure of it.
我一直想象如果我當了總統
I always imagined that if I were president,
我會請你加入我的內閣
I would want you to be a member of my cabinet.
你像個電影明星
You look like a movie star.
是光的緣故  摔倒后我經常偏頭痛
Oh, well, it's the glare. I get migraines since the fall.
-而且是突然發作  -那太遺憾了
- They can come on quite suddenly. - Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
副總統說你想當面見我
The vice president said that you wanted to meet me in person.
見到你我太高興了
It's so good to see you.
坐吧
Sit.
那樣的一摔可不是每個人都能恢復過來的  凱茜
Not everyone comes back from a fall like that, Cathy.
是啊
Yes.
我開始覺得像九命貓了
I'm starting to feel like a proverbial cat.
摘掉你的墨鏡吧  讓我看看你的眼睛
Take off your glasses, let me see your eyes.
你不缺故事可說
You have no shortage of stories.
這你知道
You know that.
我的記憶現在不太好
My memory's been very erratic lately.
有時候  我覺得我可能會
Sometimes, I think I might just forget
完全忘記自己在任時發生的事  如果...
the details of my time in office altogether if...
怎么
If?
老實說  我十分想
Honestly, I would love nothing more
向前看  總統女士
than to just move on, Madam President.
我知道你收到了工作邀約
Well, I understand that you have a job offer.
好幾份呢  很幸運
Several. I'm lucky.
艾森豪威爾戰略企劃  是吧
The Eisenhower Strategic Initiative, isn't it?
去智庫是個合理選擇  離開政府
Yes, a think tank makes sense. Outside of government.
也沒離開得很徹底
Well, not entirely outside.
而且資金主要來自...
And heavily funded by--
企業家和熱心公益者的聯盟  是的
A coalition of industrialists and civic-minded folk, yes.
有改變世界的大計劃
Big plans to change the world.
我還沒接受呢
I haven't accepted.
但你想接受
But you want to.
你覺得我不該接受嗎
You think I shouldn't take the job?
我覺得你該相信自己的直覺  凱茜
I think you should trust your gut, Cathy.
你保重
Take care of yourself.
克萊爾
Claire.
抱歉  我沒寫信向你表示悼念...
I'm sorry I didn't write after Francis--
不用道歉的
Oh, there's no need to apologize.
我還能感覺到他的手...
I can still feel his hand...
推在我后背上
on my back.
凱茜  他已經不在了
Cathy, he's gone.
比爾·謝潑德已經買通了她
Bill Shepherd got to her.
我感覺得到  她會作證的
I can feel it. She's going to testify.
我的律師告訴我她的團隊還在進行協商
My lawyers tell me her team is still negotiating,
可能還得要一陣呢
maybe for a while yet.
她覺得自己有他們  有這份工作就安全了
She thinks she's safe with them, with this job.
但其實他們是要讓她...
Instead they're gonna be sentencing her to...
得讓人以為是摔倒的并發癥
It needs to look like complications from her fall.
我可以查到她的安保隊  我還有認識人
I can have her detail pulled. I still know some people.
總會有機會的
The opportunity will present itself.
這是我們與弗蘭西斯最后的一環聯系
One last piece connecting us both to Francis.
世界要么與我們同心  要么與我們敵對  道格
The world is either with us or against us, Doug.
你會戴上嗎
You think you'll ever wear them?
感覺不對
Doesn't feel right.
知道他對我說的最后一句話嗎
Do you know the last thing he said to me?
"向我保證你和道格
"Promise me you and Doug
會照顧好彼此"
will take care of each other."
我想感謝國家美術館
I want to thank the National Gallery
組織了這場美輪美奐的展覽
for curating this magnificent exhibit.
我們希望  假以時日
Our hope is, in due time,
這些藝術品能回到它們該去的地方
these works of art will return to their rightful place
阿富汗  伊拉克  敘利亞
in Afghanistan, Iraq and Syria.
納澤先生
Mr. Nasser.
謝潑德兄妹在讓你出丑
They're making a fool of you, these Shepherds.
特別利益  中間人
The special interests. The go-betweens.
你在敘利亞所謂的維和行動成了無恥的搶地盤
Your so-called peacekeeping in Syria was a shameless land grab
犧牲的是你送去戰場的美國士兵的性命
built on the lives of American soldiers you sent into battle.
那你得怪簡·戴維斯  納澤先生
Then you can blame Jane Davis, Mr. Nasser.
我是怪她
I do.
我本想重新談
I had hoped to renegotiate
簡幾個月前促成的交易
the deal Jane helped broker many months ago.
但現在我知道那不可能了
Now I know that's impossible.
因為她剛巧沒空
Oh, because she's conveniently unavailable.
因為你根本沒這個權力
Because you're in no position to do so.
你跟我一樣  被排擠了
You've been excluded, just as I have.
他們在剝奪你的權力
They're stripping power from you.
你看過復興社會黨的行動手冊嗎
Have you ever seen the Baathist playbook?
是受了美國情報部門的啟發
It was inspired by American intelligence agencies.
有時候你得在自己國家里搞叛亂
Sometimes, you need to be an insurgent in your own country.
有意思  因為我正在
Well, that's interesting. Because presently,
跟一位已知恐怖組織成員見面呢
I'm meeting with a member of a known terrorist organization.
不好意思  我是個律師
Pardon me. But I'm a lawyer.
如果你縱容美國企業勢力
If you allow American corporate interests
斬斷哈里發國在敘利亞的未來...
to cut ICO out of Syria's future--
你是要威脅我嗎  納澤先生
Are you about to threaten me, Mr. Nasser?
不是  但我們都清楚哈里發國能做出什么事來
No, but we all know what ICO is capable of.
我只是在替我的一位委托人傳話
I'm merely conveying a message from one of my clients.
你和你的委托人是一體的
You and your client are one and the same.
美國人是如此自信他們能
Americans have such faith in their ability to
保護局勢和人民
keep things and people safe.
納澤先生  敘利亞是個
Mr. Nasser, Syria is a country of...
曾經有學校  家園和清真寺的國家
former schools, former homes, former places of worship.
你的組織是制造破壞的主要勢力
Your organization played a large part in the destruction.
你也是  總統女士
And so have you, Madam President.
我恐怕幫不了你
I'm afraid I can't help you.
是啊
No...
你是幫不了
you can't.
我有兩個女兒  美麗的妻子
I got two daughters, a beautiful wife.
盡了職
Paid my dues.
做了四屆
Four terms.
多元化選區的共和黨人
A Republican in a diverse district.
我在當地的政績傲人
I got a ground operation second to none.
我的志愿者
And my volunteers,
在他們之后
their sons and their daughters
他們的孩子也都追隨我
are coming up right behind 'em. I just...
讓我覺得
I just feel like, um...
我的時機可能到了
this could be my moment, you know?
弗萊德跟我說了即將推出的立法
Fred told me about the legislation about to be introduced.
我要聯署
I'm co-signing.
-是...  -很有野心
- It's-- - Ambitious.
史無前例
It's unprecedented.
有兩黨的支持
It's bipartisan, is what it is.
你為她工作
You worked for her.
我為她丈夫工作
I worked for her husband.
沒人希望她控制核武公文包
Nobody wants her hands on a nuclear football.
或是把軍隊派去任何地方  不論國內國外
Or sending any more uniforms anywhere, here or abroad.
你只能接受這一點
You're gonna have to be okay with that.
你接受嗎
Are you?
我不欠她什么
I owe her nothing.
他們有你什么把柄
So what do they have on you?
等等  哥們
Hold on, slugger.
我們還沒那么熟呢
I'm still trying to get acquainted here.
-好吧  -你去哪
- Right. - Where do you think you're going?
弗萊德·安博格叫我來見你
Fred Amburg asked me to meet you.
-弗萊德也叫我來見你  -我們見過了
- Well, Fred asked me to meet you. - And we've met.
你圖個什么啊
Where do you get off?
-就你的經歷而言  -我去的地方
- After where you've been. - You mean where I was.
安博格先生也在
With Mr. Amburg.
你的上一位老板
The last person you worked for--
成了美國總統
Became the President of the United States.
他把你趕出去了
He pushed you out.
我是你的機會
I am your chance.
雖然我不用向你或任何人
You know, not that I have to prove myself to you,
證明自己
or to anyone else,
但我找得到漏洞
but I can find the opening,
裂口  薄弱點
the crack, the weak spot.
我不知道
I don't know,
或許看得清人的恐懼是種詛咒
maybe it's a curse to know what people fear.
比如你
Like you.
我覺得你害怕的  議員
I think what scares you, Congressman.
你的選民
Your base,
你的本地政績  人民的愛戴
your ground game, all that love.
讓你覺得這是你應得的
You thought you deserved it,
這只屬于你  而不是別人
that it was meant for you and nobody else.
你盲目了
You got blind.
你忘了他們也會找你的麻煩
You forgot that they'd come for you.
他們會來的
But they will come.
這一行就是如此
That's how this business is built.
所以我再問你一次
So, I'm going to ask you again.
他們有你什么把柄
What is it that they have on you?
我的選區包括芝加哥奧黑爾機場
My district covers O'Hare.
養老金
Pensions.
行李工的  我...
The baggage handlers. I--
該死
Shit.
真是犯蠢
It was stupid.
嗯
Well...
不能解決掉才叫蠢呢
it's only stupid if you can't make it go away.
湯姆  冷靜點
Tom, calm down.
我已經太老  做不到禮貌了
I'm getting too old to be polite.
聽聽協議條件  報道內容不會變的
Hear the deal out. Content will not be changed.
你和我都清楚那不是真的
And you and I both know better.
那晚上發生了什么事
Something happened that night.
他們的婚姻已破裂
Their marriage was broken,
他去了白宮
he went over there.
我不是說這有關聯
I'm not saying they're connected,
但他第二天就死了
but the next day he winds up dead.
而她早知道他要遭起訴
She knew an indictment was coming.
你明白這意味著什么嗎
Do you understand what that means?
那就接著寫報道啊
Then keep writing.
好讓他們發推特騙點擊量嗎
So they can turn it into a 140 characters for clickbait?
我們不做報道了
We don't write anymore,
我們不過是在做豬食
we come up with feed for the trough.
馬上把那玩意放下  否則我砸了它
Put that goddamn thing down before I smash it!
你得回去
You need to go back in there
道歉
and apologize.
對誰道歉  戴娜
To whom, Dayna?
我們的新老板就是一個揚聲器里的聲音
Our new boss is a voice on a speakerphone!
他都不知道我已經出去了
He doesn't even know I walked out.
我們為什么不報道加德納分析
Why don't we write about how Gardner Analytics
買下了好多電視臺
is buying up television stations
和國內一些最好的報紙
and some of the greatest papers in this country?
"分析"  天吶
"Analytics." Oh, my God.
這叫什么名字
What the fuck does that even mean?
尸檢結果
According to the autopsy,
是自然死亡
natural causes.
心臟病嗎
Heart attack?
肝臟藥物服用過量
Overdose of his liver medication.
推測為意外
Accidental, presumably.
-你有什么沒告訴我  -沒有了
- What aren't you telling me? - Nothing.
他絕不會有意那么做的
He would never do that intentionally.
當晚海亞當斯酒店大堂的目擊者稱
Witnesses in the lobby of the Hay-Adams that night
前總統看上去很凌亂
said the former president was acting disoriented.
你跟他的遺孀說過這些嗎
Did you share this with his widow?
就是她在要我調查
She's the one who asked me to look into it.
她懷疑是謝潑德兄妹
She suspects the Shepherds.
他當時常跟他們見面  但那晚沒有
He was with them a lot, but not that night.
-那誰在  -除了她嗎
- And who was? - Other than her?
那可是她丈夫  道格
That was her husband, Doug.
她是總統
She's the president.
你還真忠心啊  納森
Don't you sound devoted, Nathan.
我跟她只有職業層面的接觸
My only contact with her is in my official capacity.
你以為不會再見到我了嗎
Did you think you'd seen the last of me?
我才不會那么想呢
That's the last thing I thought.
我就當做是稱贊了
I'll take that as a compliment.
道格  給
Doug, here.
我追查了他的行蹤
I tracked his comings and goings
一直查到他離開白宮后
back to when he left the White House.
我拿到了他電腦接收的元數據
I got my hands on the metadata going into his computer.
莉安·哈維的手機攝像頭在撞車時還在傳輸
LeAnn Harvey's camera phone was streaming during the crash.
信號直接與一個IP地址相連
A direct feed to only one IP address.
弗蘭西斯的
Francis'.
他的筆記本
His laptop.
看著讓人難受  但...
It's not easy to watch, but...
-好  -你自己決定吧
- Okay. - Up to you.
漢默施密特先生
Mr. Hammerschmidt.
鄧肯·謝潑德
Duncan Shepherd.
抱歉下午的會議我沒能親自到場
I'm sorry I couldn't be at the meeting in person this afternoon.
如果我下班晚  遛狗員就會送它過來
My walker drops him off when it's late.
來
Come.
你看到了我的爆發
You saw my little outburst.
我很喜歡
I enjoyed it.
你的憤怒
The outrage.
我們需要更多這個
We need more of it.
我尤其喜歡你前幾晚在電視上的露面
I especially liked your appearance on television the other night.
嗯
Yeah. Well...
我有時候會比較激動
I get a little heated sometimes.
這正是《先驅報》需要的曝光
It's exactly the kind of exposure the Herald needs.
湯姆
Tom,
你現在是一個影響廣泛
you're now part of a conglomerate
人脈發達的大集團的一員了
with vast influence and reach.
我要說的是  你需要什么證據我都能找來
The point is I can bring you whatever evidence you need.
-等等  -離婚換赦免
- Hold on. - Divorce for pardon.
這是有幾分真實的  但你的消息源...
There's a kernel of truth to it, but your source...
你開口前  先想想我能給你什么
And before you say anything, consider what I'm offering.
伸張正義的機會
An opportunity for justice.
如果你是說編造證據  謝潑德先生
If you're talking about manufacturing evidence, Mr. Shepherd,
-我沒興趣  -我不覺得
- I'm not interested. - Beg to differ.
拜托別拿老記者的那套來壓我
And spare me the seasoned journalist routine, please.
你在這行干了30年
Your 30 years in the business.
我跟你的老助理安吉拉談過
I've spoken to your old assistant, Angela.
她寫了一篇關于與你共事的報道
She's written a piece about her time with you.
我可以發布  也可以...
I could run it, or...
你曾經對弗蘭克·安德伍德像狗一般緊咬不放
Your dogged pursuit of Frank Underwood, pardon the pun,
現在改追著他的女人了
is now your pursuit of his bride.
想想吧
Think about it.
你這年紀的男人  如今都很容易崩潰
Men your age, they unravel very easily these days.
文森特·阿布佐法官有資質
Judge Vincent Abruzzo has the credentials.
有發表論著  有公開聲明
The published writings, the public statements.
全都沒問題  都齊了
It all checks out. Full package.
所以你為什么遲遲不決定啊  總統女士
So what's the hesitation, Madam Prez?
首都電視是加德納分析的子公司
Beltway Television is owned by Gardner Analytics.
是鄧肯·謝潑德的最新創造
It's the latest brainchild of Duncan Shepherd.
我已經回避了一切
So far, I've deflected
關于科魯茲小姐言論的問題
all questions regarding Ms. Cruz's commentary.
很好  不要回應她
Good. Let's not dignify it.
行了  謝謝
No. That's fine, thank you.
就是有這個問題  但我忍不住
They were a hazard, I couldn't resist.
抱歉我沒參加葬禮  還念《詩篇》了嗎
Sorry I missed the funeral. Were there psalms?
第42段
Number 42.
我喜歡那個
I love 42.
納澤不該直接找到你
Nasser had no business coming to you directly.
我知道如果我見他  你就會突然出現
Well, I knew if I met with him, you'd suddenly appear.
他覺得被騙了  簡
He feels lied to, Jane.
因為確實如此
Because he was.
我們根本沒打算給那些土匪一席位置
We were never gonna give those bandits a seat at the table.
簡  他威脅說哈里發國會再發動襲擊
Jane, he's threatened more ICO attacks.
哈里發國基本上都被消滅了
ICO is neutralized, mostly.
我們該重新考慮在敘利亞的行動了
It's time to re-think our involvement in Syria.
撤軍  重建
Stand down, rebuild.
這個協議對于我們所有人都很重要
This deal is important for all of us.
包括謝潑德兄妹
Including the Shepherds.
我也不喜歡他們家族
Look, I'm no fan of that family,
但在敘利亞問題上  我們的利益是一致的
but in the case of Syria, our interests align.
我們下一階段
The next phase of our...
在該地區的行動
presence in the region
更多是為了戰利品而不是和平了
is more about the spoils than the peace.
問題在于佩特羅夫
The problem is Petrov,
謝潑德兄妹和我都鄙視他
whom the Shepherds and I despise.
你有謝潑德家族什么把柄
What do you have on the Shepherds?
跟你有聯系的那幾家機構
I'm sure one of the several agencies you're
肯定有一家有料
involved with has something.
你不是給每個和你打交道的人都建立份檔案嗎
And don't you keep files on everyone you're dealing with?
比爾和安奈特都很小心
Bill and Annette are very careful.
那安奈特的兒子鄧肯呢
What about Annette's son, Duncan?
馬克比我更了解他們
Well, Mark knows them more than I do.
我覺得對于前總統還有更好的選擇
I thought there were better options for a former president...
但安奈特不肯放過弗蘭克
but Annette wouldn't leave Frank alone.
那就是他們的問題  他們不知何時該收手
That's their problem, they don't know when to stop.
你三個月前離開時
You know, when you left three months ago,
我還想你去了哪
I wondered where you'd gone.
然后  我就再沒想你了
And then, I didn't think of you at all.
你那么說
You say that.
但我在你的眼里看到了痛苦  總統女士
But I detect pain in your eyes, Madam President.
就像渴望甘泉的小鹿
As a deer longs for streams of water.
我如此渴望你  上帝
So I long for you, God.
你想他嗎
Do you miss him?
上帝嗎  總在想
God? Always.
我希望你搬到白宮里來跟我住  簡
I'd like you to move in here with me, Jane, into the White House.
我需要你的建議
I need your counsel
以及你對馬克的了解
and your perspective when it comes to Mark.
事實上  去年一整年在白宮
The truth is that whole last year in the White House...
我完全迷失了
I just lost myself.
最瘋狂的是  我都沒見過佐伊·巴恩斯
And the crazy thing is, I've never even met Zoe Barnes.
你也這么跟聯邦檢察官說的嗎
Is that what you told the US Attorney?
還是你和克萊爾·安德伍德做了交易
Or did you and Claire Underwood make a deal?
我和總統分道揚鑣了
The president and I are on different paths.
你是說你沒見過她
You're saying you haven't seen her.
我們談過
We've spoken.
我就是不覺得她的白宮里有我的位置
I just don't see a role for me in her White House.
我在給科爾議員工作
I'm working with Congressman Cole.
他要競選議長
He's making a play for speaker.
我今天從《先驅報》辭職了
I left the Herald today.
如果你是為了這個找我
If that's why you wanted to see me,
-想讓我給你的新老板做報道  -不是
- make a pitch for your new guy. - No.
不  這是在做彌補
No, this is about making amends.
-我去年秋天又開始喝酒了  -不
- Last fall I started drinking again. - No.
你選這里
You picked this place
是因為這里到處是博主和國會山的鼠輩
because it's full of bloggers and Hill rats.
現在  這里的人都能看到我們在說話
Right now, everyone here can see us talking together,
客客氣氣的
like civilized people.
就好像我不曾在報紙上喊你"殺人犯"
As if I never called you a murderer in print.
你最新一篇關于弗蘭西斯的報道
Your latest article on Francis.
關于他死前的幾晚
This story about the nights leading up to his death?
-你想彌補嗎  -你的消息源是誰
- You want to make amends? - Who are your sources?
彼得·羅素
Peter Russo.
佐伊·巴恩斯
Zoe Barnes.
莉安·哈維
LeAnn Harvey.
道格  你已經沒有陰影可躲了
Doug, there isn't a shadow for you to hide in anymore.
唯一知道一切的人  就是你
The only person knows everything is you.
我不全知道
I don't.
放棄他吧
Let him go.
我不知道你什么意思
I don't know what you're talking about.
你早晚得做出決定
At some point, you're gonna have to decide.
克萊爾·安德伍德  相信我
Claire Underwood, believe me,
等時候到了  她會找上你的
she'll come for you when it's time.
謝謝
Thanks.
那玩意有咖啡因的
You know, there's caffeine in that.
我知道
I do.
我喜歡你愛喝阿諾德·帕爾默  但...
I love that you love Arnold Palmers, but--
指發明這種飲品的高爾夫球手
他可是個偉人
Arnold Palmer was a great man.
還在想她嗎
She still on your mind?
這樣下去不行
This arrangement isn't working.
怎樣
Which arrangement?
馬克  到床上來
Mark, come to bed.
她得覺得自己有點自主權
She needs to feel some degree of autonomy.
去他的自主權
Fuck autonomy.
她要為我們服務
She serves at our pleasure.
她肯定覺得自己不受重視
I'm sure she feels undervalued.
不受重視
Undervalued?
克萊爾·黑爾  得了
Claire Hale? Please.
要是比爾不能好起來呢
What if Bill doesn't get better?
他好多了
He is better.
如果在明面上
If we don't play this right,
我們不能做好  就注定要失敗
in the public eye, we are doomed to fail.
-你明白吧  -是她要完蛋
- You know that, right? - She's doomed, you mean.
聽著
Look...
我們說清楚
Let's be clear.
我對她沒有感覺  但她得把我視為伙伴
I am not attracted to her, but she needs to see me as a partner.
而且急什么
And what is the rush?
比爾要法庭的多數支持
Bill wants a majority on the court.
他等了很久了
He's waited a long time.
至少讓她有個總統的樣兒
Let her at least look like the president.
之后如果有必要  我會攪黃她的提名人
I'll scuttle the nomination if it comes to that later.
是我要阿布佐法官  馬克
I want Judge Abruzzo, Mark.
永遠別質疑我哥哥能不能
And don't ever question my brother's ability
發揮最大的本事
to function at the highest level.
西爾維婭·普拉斯[作家]那句話怎么說的
What is that Sylvia Plath line?
"她像吸氣一般吞食男人"
"She eats men like air."
這是說誰呢
Who are we talking about?
抱歉我們昨天沒碰到
Sorry we missed each other yesterday.
很抱歉今天又要讓你為難了
Well, my apologies for leaving you in the lurch again today.
沒事吧
Everything okay?
我跟安奈特談過了
I spoke to Annette.
我真心認為這是最佳辦法
I really think this is the best course.
-你見過喬治嗎  -誰
- Did you ever meet George? - George?
我弟弟喬治  平凡的喬治
My brother George. Incurious George.
不  沒見過
No, I never did.
想當年
And back in the old days,
我們在中西部買下了一個廠子
we acquired an operation in the Midwest,
精煉加拿大原油
refining Canadian crude.
利潤...
Profit margin was...
令人吃驚
It was staggering.
但喬治
But George,
卻突然崇高了起來
he got all high-minded about it.
覺得我們違法太多  于是
Thought that we were bending too many laws. So he--
他買下了一家對手公司  環保能源的那種
He bought a rival company, green energy type,
然后起訴了我們
and he sued us.
起訴我們啊
Sued us.
真是的
I mean...
這樣的背叛
The betrayal.
我父親真正信仰的  是家庭
My father's true religion was family.
他很心寒
And he was troubled.
他對喬治的所作所為非常心寒
He was deeply troubled by what George had done.
改了遺囑
Changed his will.
他死前
Any sibling bringing litigation
任何起訴過其他兄妹的子女
against any other at the time of his death
將自動失去他或她的那份遺產
would automatically lose their share of the inheritance.
每一分該死的錢
Every damnable penny.
他就這么說的
He used that word.
而喬治就這樣失去了繼承權
Which is exactly what happened to George.
他不敢相信
George couldn't believe it.
還說是我哄騙爸爸那么做的
Accused me of tricking Dad into doing it
因為他已經虛弱得神志不清了
when he was too weak to know his own mind.
我父親心里從來都很清楚
My father always knew his own mind.
喬治
George...
他傷心透了
...he was just so broken up about it.
都沒對遺囑做出抗爭
Didn't even contest the will.
而在我看來
Which as far as I see it,
這意味著他就不配
it means he had no place inheriting
繼承那樣的錢
that kind of money to begin with.
他本來有他所需要的一切
The man had everything he ever needed.
但他太...
He was just so...
短視
Short-sighted.
現在住在緬因州的一個島上
Lives on some island in Maine now.
知道對于我來說最糟的部分是什么嗎
You know what the worst part for me was?
這讓安奈特多傷心
How much it upset Annette.
這不行
That was a no-go.
我會拿到提名的  比爾
I'll get the nomination, Bill.
再見了  馬克
Bye-bye now, Mark.
他們好心
They were good enough to
給了我一個大堂的外線
provide me with a direct feed from the Hall.
-這真有必要嗎  -吸氣
- Is this necessary? - Inhale.
你看過《吉賽爾》嗎
You ever seen Giselle?
別那么看我
Don't look at me like that.
也不都是壞結果
The results aren't all bad.
我被監視了
I'm being watched.
誰
By whom?
湯姆·漢默施密特  聯邦檢察官
Tom Hammerschmidt, the US Attorney.
我覺得這已經有段時間了
It's a feeling that I've had for a while.
喂
Hello?
我在
I'm here.
太冒險了
It's too risky.
如果是弗蘭西斯提的  你就會找到辦法
If Francis had asked, you'd have found a way.
沒錯
That's true.
那我很遺憾
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
看來我們要分道揚鑣了  道格
I guess this is where we part ways, Doug.
這樣最好
It's for the best.
那道別吧
Then say goodbye.
知道他對我說的最后一句話是什么嗎
You know what the last thing he said to me was?
"我無法想象你們中
"I can't imagine a world
有一個不在了世界會是什么樣"
with only one of you in it."
每段關系發展到一定時候  你都會想知道
There comes a point in every relationship where you wonder,
"你跟我是一邊的嗎"
"Are you with me?"
是嗎
Are you?
比爾·謝潑德想利用
So, there are some loose ends
一些遺留問題
that Bill Shepherd is trying to exploit.
一個是
One being...
凱茜·杜蘭特
Cathy Durant.
我們認識很久了
And I have known each other for a very long time.
我知道
I know.
我上次見到凱茜時  她像是一腳踩在鬼門關上
Well, the last time I saw Cathy, she looked at death's door.
你不能要我那么做
You can't ask that of me.
她信任你  簡
She trusts you, Jane.
她信任你
She trusts you.
這是在光天化日下動手
That's making a move in broad daylight.
我喜歡有你住這兒
I enjoy having you here.
我會永遠無法原諒自己的
I'll never be able to forgive myself.
你告訴他莉安的事后呢
And when you told him about LeAnn?
他沒表露出什么情緒  女士
He showed no emotion, ma'am.
-他現在在哪  -還在家
- Where is he now? - Still at home.
我找了幾個探員跟蹤他
I have a couple of agents trailing him.
在聯調局看來  這是為了保護道格
As far as the Bureau is concerned, it's for Doug's own safety.
除了科爾議員  他還見誰了嗎
And besides Congressman Cole, has he met with anyone?
除了我  還有湯姆·漢默施密特
Other than myself, Tom Hammerschmidt.
或許你該去跟他
Perhaps you should be the one on him.
以防我們什么時候需要單獨跟他談
In case we need to find him alone at some point.
我還是很擔心他的精神狀態
I continue to be very concerned about his state of mind.
是  女士
Yes, ma'am.
弗蘭西斯在手寫遺囑里把一切都給了他
Francis left him everything in his handwritten will.
我好奇嗎  是的
Am I curious? Yes.
但那也不想等著道格拉斯·斯坦普扳倒我
But not enough to wait for Douglas Stamper to bring me down.
杜蘭特國務卿  戴維斯女士在后面
Secretary Durant, Ms. Davis is in the back.
-塞爾呢  -他沒當班  我是吉安卡洛
- Where's Sal? - He's off. My name is Giancarlo.
認識您很高興
It's a pleasure to meet you.
這邊請
Right this way.
今天人很少
Very slow today.
請
Please.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-國務卿女士  請  -抱歉
- Madam Secretary, please. - I'm sorry, I'm--
國務卿女士
Madam Secretary.
簡  你怎么能
Jane, how could you?
你怎么能這么對我
How could you do this to me?
-聽我說  親愛的  -不  你聽我說
- Listen to me, sweetheart. - No, you listen to me.
是克萊爾嗎
Is this Claire?
你是為了她嗎
Are you doing this for her?
凱茜
Oh, Cathy.
一旦決定已下  你就逃不掉了
Once the decision is made, you can't escape.
或許今天不會  但是
Maybe it won't happen today, but...
總有一天
someday,
恐怕總有那一天
someday, I'm afraid.
我詛咒你
I curse you.
我詛咒你  愿你死得很痛苦
I curse you and wish you a painful death.
漫長而極其痛苦
Drawn out and excruciating.
我不想讓你失望
I don't want to disappoint you.
但我不會那樣死的
That's not how I'm gonna die.
走著瞧吧
Well, we'll see.
是吧
Will we?
我考慮了提名的事
I've been thinking about the nomination.
你應該選阿布佐
You should go with Abruzzo.
如果發出了錯誤信號
We could get beaten up in the midterms
中期選舉時可能會受打擊
if the wrong signals are sent.
這樣可以成為連任總統
It's the way to be a two-term president.
我們還可以成就很多
There's still a lot we can accomplish.
你真是個怪人
You're such a strange animal.
你當上副總統后
You've never been comfortable in your skin
就一直不舒服
since you've been vice president.
你為什么還要費這個心
Why did you even try?
我相信你
I believe in you.
那可不夠
Well, that's not enough.
那我不打擾你看電影了
I'll leave you to your movie then.
安奈特對這一切怎么看
What does Annette have to say about all this?
-我知道你們很親密  -我不會背叛她的
- I know you're close to her. - I won't betray her.
就像我也不會背叛你  克萊爾
Just like I won't betray you, Claire.
他們制住我們了
They got us, you know?
我們應該宣布了
We should make the announcement.
阿布佐
Abruzzo.
開始放吧
You can start the film.
她已經見過了環保署地區行政人員
She's already met with the EPA Regional Administrator,
找備忘錄
looking for memos.
硬盤已清空  云端也沒留東西
Hard disks have been scrubbed, and there's nothing in the cloud.
沒有文件  電子和紙質都沒有
There's no paper trail, virtual or otherwise.
-斯克斯基  -她曾是《先驅報》的
- Skorsky? - She was with the Herald.
我加入白宮時離開了那里
She left when I joined the White House.
就是個當地報紙  我們可以買下來
It's just a local paper. We can acquire it.
這不是總統的嘩眾取寵
This isn't about the president grandstanding.
她有線人
She's talking to someone.
-鄧肯  -我們應該為中期選舉留著應用
- Duncan-- - We should save the app for the midterms.
你相不相信你做的東西
Well, do you trust what you've built or not?
我不希望被曝光
I don't want it exposed.
她也用了應用
She signed up for the app.
我們可以侵入她的手機  打探一番
We can get into her phone, take a look around.
可以讓我們單獨談談嗎
Would you gentlemen excuse us?
不  留下吧  比爾
No, stay. Bill.
她要見我
She wants to see me.
不
Nope.
她說馬克已經不是個稱職的副總統了
She says Mark is no longer a viable vice president.
不能傳達她的意愿
He's not communicating her wishes.
她要直接跟我談
She wants to deal directly with me.
她根本無權做任何要求
She's in no position to demand anything.
天吶
My God.
你想去見她
You want to meet with her.
她始終是總統
She's still the president.
曾三次墮胎
Who had three abortions,
還在這事上對美國人民撒謊
lied to the American people about one.
我說了  我不想用那個
I told you, I'm not willing to use that.
那你就用另一個
Then you'll use the other thing.
馬克告訴我們的
What Mark told us.
封存了  案子挺典型的
Seal. The case was pretty typical.
預科學校嗑藥
Prep school drugs.
鄧肯·謝潑德有足夠的錢脫罪  但另一個男孩
Duncan Shepherd was rich enough to get off, but the other boy,
就沒那么幸運了
not so lucky.
但是
But...
轉錄內容啊
the transcript.
-有趣的讀物  -是令人痛苦
- Fascinating read. - Painful, really.
謝潑德女士來了
Ms. Shepherd's here.
叫她進來
Oh, please send her in.
-安奈特  -克萊爾
- Annette. - Claire.
-簡  -安奈特
- Jane. - Annette.
很高興我們都能直呼彼此的名字了
I'm honored we've graduated to a first name basis.
姓氏有時是個負擔
Surnames can be a burden.
有意思
That's funny.
我一直喜歡我的姓呢
I've always loved mine.
你呢  克萊爾  你放棄了你的娘家姓
What about you, Claire? You gave yours up.
是啊
Exactly.
覺得更像個安德伍德嗎
You feel more like an Underwood?
就像你說的  姓氏有時是負擔
Well, like you said. Surnames can be a burden.
我喜歡你的
I like your...
-女性風格  -女人是什么
- lady quotes. - What is woman?
德·波伏瓦的問題
De Beauvoir question.
沒錯  《第二性》里的
That's right. From The Second Sex?
記得那堂課嗎  安奈特
Remember that class, Annette?
作為少女  那感覺多怪啊
How strange it was, as a teenager,
被一個男人用法語教女權主義
to be taught feminism by a man in French.
我討厭那本書
I hated that book.
的確很啰嗦
Long-winded, for sure.
但你得承認
But you gotta admit.
她什么都說對了
She was right about everything.
跟我合作吧
Work with me.
直接商談  不要中間人
Directly, without a middleman.
馬克如果不頂用
What use is Mark,
又有什么用呢
if he can't be effective?
馬克是可以很有用的
Mark can be very effective.
但現在兩邊都不滿意
Well, but both sides are unhappy.
最高法院
The Supreme Court.
這是一個
This is a choice
能超越總統任期的決定
that outlives any presidency.
沒錯
Exactly.
但也是總統的重要政績之一
But also part of what defines a presidency.
當然
Of course.
所以我不能...
So I can't be...
我可以考慮一切信息充足的意見
I will consider any informed opinion.
但我  你明白吧
But I... You understand.
這必須我來決定  安妮
The decision has to be mine, Annie.
已經沒人那么喊我了
No one calls me that anymore.
你兒子  他多大了
Your son, how old is he now?
27嗎  不對
Twenty-seven? No...
28了  我似乎總把他記小一年
Twenty-eight. I always seem to make him a year younger.
他看上去總是比實際年齡年輕
He always did look young for his age.
尤其是少年時的收監照
Especially his juvenile mugshot.
一張娃娃臉
Such a baby face.
你會跟比爾商量一下嗎
So, you'll speak to Bill?
不必
I don't need to.
你是總統  你該按自己的想法做事
You're the president. You should do what you want.
我也總這么想
That's what I keep thinking.
記得我們以前原本多快樂嗎
Do you remember how much fun we used to have,
直到我們明白了規矩
before we understood the rules?
先別急著徹底跟她決裂  好嗎
Look, let's not let it all break down here, okay?
如果我說錯了糾正我
Correct me if I'm wrong,
但你此前從未在白宮
but you've never had a foothold
有如此的影響力  所以
like this in the White House. So...
你是想挽救她  還是上她
You want to save her or fuck her?
不管怎樣  私下里去做
Either way, do it on your time.
別變成私人恩怨
Don't make it personal.
別侮辱我
Don't insult me.
讓她聽話
Shut her down.
給她看
Show it to her.
這是我和比爾的意思  你得照做
That's what Bill and I want. And you'll do it.
不
No.
-這不是請求  -這會造成的后果
- I'm not asking. - The fallout from that...
我不在乎
Not my concern.
你會在乎的
It will be your concern.
你沒靠山了
You're on your own now.
-不不  我們完了  -別
- Oh, no, no, we're done. - Don't.
安奈特
Annette.
中年白人男子的統治結束了
The reign of the middle-aged white man is over.
比爾·謝潑德這樣不肯放手的人
The Bill Shepherds of the world who won't let go,
必須下臺
have to go.
拍下來的服務員
The waitress who filmed
是謝潑德自由基金會的人
it works for the Shepherd Freedom Foundation.
他們本想用這個
They were hoping to use the clip
推動阿布佐法官的提名表決
when it came to Judge Abruzzo's confirmation.
好  謝謝
Okay, thank you.
你有湯姆·耶茨的消息嗎  凱爾茜
Have you heard from Tom Yates, Kelsey?
沒有
No.
你跟他挺好的  是吧
You were friendly with him, right?
我好久沒有湯姆的消息了
I haven't heard from Tom in a long time.
你的同事呢  他們打聽過他嗎
And your coworkers, have they asked about him at all?
偶爾吧
Now and then.
他以前常去那里
He used to roam around down there.
大家都喜歡他
Everyone liked him.
我已經讓我的國安團隊去查了
Well, I had my national security team look into it.
他們找到了他
And they tracked him down.
據說他在布拉格周邊
It seems he's been using his credit card
用過信用卡
in and around Prague, apparently.
那太好了
I'm glad to hear it.
就是  我還擔心來著
No, because I was worried.
我們以前還經常聯絡  但突然就斷了
We used to talk a lot, and then it just stopped.
你讀過他寫的東西嗎
Did you ever read anything he was working on...
除了他給我寫的講稿
...besides the speeches he wrote for me?
除了早年那些沒有了
No, just the early stuff.
凱茜
Cathy.
斯坦啊
Oh, Stan.
天吶
Oh, my God.
沒別的事了
That's all for now.
什么時候的事
When did it happen?
我太遺憾了
I'm so, so sorry.
不  我上次跟她談話時
No, the last conversation I had with her,
她還在說她的新工作
she was talking about her new job
以及那本該是多么好的機會
and what a great opportunity it was going to be.
總統女士
Madam President.
抱歉我這么晚打來
Forgive me for calling so late.
我剛得到通知
I've just been informed...
凱瑟琳·杜蘭特死了
that Catherine Durant is dead.
栓塞  據說是跟她的摔倒有關
It's an embolism, they're saying. Connected to her fall.
我想謝謝你  道格  你幫了大忙
I want to thank you, Doug, so much for your help.
真遺憾
It's a shame.
太遺憾了
It's a terrible shame.
是啊
Yes...
太遺憾了
a terrible, terrible shame.
人們會懷念她的
She will be missed.
馬克
Mark.
抱歉打擾你跑步
Apologies for disturbing your run.
怎么了
What's happened?
-可以單獨說句話嗎  -好
- Can we have a word in private? - Of course.
沒事  史蒂夫  我的保鏢已查過這一帶了
It's okay, Steve. My detail cleared the area.
-安全  -好  安全
- Clear. - Okay, we're clear.
我們去哪
Where are we going?
你有20秒
You have 20 seconds.
我可以處理掉他  否則警察就會找到他
I can get rid of this, or the cops will find him.
你已經沒有選擇了  總統女士
You've run out of options, Madam President.
我知道了
I understand.
美國最高法院設有九名大法官  往往其中八人在意識形態上左右各半
而總有一名在斷案時忽左忽右  成為決定案情的最關鍵一票
今年夏天"搖擺票"肯尼迪法官宣布退休
特朗普提名布雷特·卡瓦諾接替肯尼迪的席位
因為卡瓦諾是保守派  一旦他成功任命  最高法院勢必整體右傾
在參議院舉行的任命聽證過程中  反對黨民主黨議員們雖然百般努力
但是因席位不夠  所以無力阻擋卡瓦諾進軍最高法院的腳步
然而9月16日  《華盛頓郵報》刊文  報道加州一名大學教授
克里斯汀·福特稱高中時在一次聚會上曾遭到卡瓦諾性侵未遂
雖然卡瓦諾立即發表聲明斷然否認性侵指控
但民主黨迅速抓住機會要求白宮撤換卡瓦諾
媒體則如同打了興奮劑一樣全天候轟炸式地對性侵指控進行報道
9月27日  參議院召開公開聽證會
福特首先出場  雖然對于那次聚會的很多細節都回憶不起來
但她表示自己"百分百"確定卡瓦諾就是當年的施暴者
福特發言時表情真摯  回答訊問從容鎮定  談及性侵事件  聲音顫抖
幾個小時下來  觀者無不動容  社交網絡上輿論幾乎一面倒地同情福特
但卡瓦諾靠聽證會下半場的"激情自辯"扳回了局面
他在開場陳詞中不僅堅決否認自己是施暴者
還控訴民主黨議員利用福特給自己栽上莫須有的罪名
在談及此事對自己的家庭帶來的巨大傷害時  聲音哽咽幾難成言
在問答環節  卡瓦諾對民主黨議員們的嚴厲質詢
給予了毫不客氣的反駁  甚至進行反問  輿論的天平就這樣被扳了回來
10月6日下午  參議院以50比48的表決結果正式確認了卡瓦諾的大法官任命
一名共和黨投了反對票  一名民主黨投了贊成票  其余議員都是按黨站隊
卡瓦諾成為1881年以來任命投票時結果最為接近的一名大法官
而卡瓦諾的激情自辯讓共和黨支持者認為
他受到了民主黨和媒體的雙重政治迫害
這種情緒被共和黨政客們轉化為了催票利器
卡瓦諾正式任命后  多個民調顯示共和黨選民投票熱情大幅提升
在11月6日的中期選舉中  那些投票反對卡瓦諾任命的民主黨參議員紛紛落馬
唯一投票支持任命卡瓦諾的民主黨參議員曼欽則順利連任
美國的各類工會組織實力強大  在同民主黨結成政治同盟之后
同民主黨政客互相扶持  在政客競選時出錢出力出人
而政客上臺后則會通過一系列對工會有利的法律法規
多年以來  由于影響力巨大  加上又有政治保護傘
所以很多大工會組織內部腐敗不斷  不少甚至成為準黑幫組織
涉及敲詐勒索  偷竊洗錢  非法賭博等等違法勾當
而挪用盜用工會成員的養老金也是被媒體揭露出來的工會黑幕之一
據報道  美國最大的一家工會成員養老金基金
因經營不善  曾經申請破產  涉及金額超過百億美元
在芝加哥地區  當地最大的工會組織頭目科力及其整個家族
控制工會多年  同芝加哥地區的各路政客也都稱兄道弟